celtx.com 2009-12-25

# Celtx - Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is designed to assist you in understanding how Celtx uses and safeguards the information and resources that you provide to us.

Celtx provides the Celtx Software ("Software") and manages operations of the Celtx Web Site, the Celtx Studios and Celtx Project Central (collectively, "Services"). The Services may require registration, and the selection of usernames and passwords, in order to function.

Use of Information

CELTX DOES NOT SELL, RENT, LOAN, TRADE, LEASE OR OTHERWISE TRANSFER ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH THE CELTX SOFTWARE OR SERVICES TO ANY THIRD PARTY.

Celtx may collect information which is required in order for the Services to verify your identity. This includes your username and password. You are personally responsible for safeguarding your username and password.

The Celtx website may contain forms and forums where feedback and other comments can be reported directly to Celtx (the �Forums�). Information which is voluntarily submitted to the Forums is used to improve the Celtx Services. Celtx reserves the right to utilize this information for marketing purposes, for instance by displaying selected comments on the Celtx website or in other communications. If Celtx chooses to display a user-submitted comment it will either display it anonymously, stripping away all personally identifiable information, or request permission directly from you before displaying any such personally identifiable information.

No System Information Collected

No information concerning your computing facilities is collected that is not related to providing Celtx Services. No information about your computing facilities will be provided to any third party without your express permission.

Delete/Deactivation Policy

If you wish to modify or delete any personal information you submitted to Celtx, you may do so by either modifying your profile on the Forums or contacting us at [info@celtx.com](mailto:info@celtx.com). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete all such information within fifteen working days from the date of the receipt of your request. Please note that it may be impossible to delete a user's entry without some residual information remaining in our system due to the presence of Celtx maintained backups and records of deletions. Celtx reserves the right not to delete information in order to comply with applicable local laws or regulations.
